rtpr.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy-Policy | Real Time Pain Relief

## You are here

Home / Privacy-Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which RTPR LLC. collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the rtpr.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by RTPR LLC..

Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, place an order, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

Web browser cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

How we use collected information

RTPR LLC. collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:

To process transactions  
We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.

To send periodic emails   
The email address Users provide for order processing, will only be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. 

Also, we use Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting for Remarketing with Google Analytics and Google Display Network Impression Reporting. To opt out of Google Analytics you can visit <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>  and/or [https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/ ](https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/%C2%A0)

How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. Our Site is also in compliance with PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for Users.

Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

Changes to this privacy policy

RTPR LLC. has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

RTPR LLC.  
rtpr.com  
P.O. Box 798  
Cabot, AR. 72023  
877-787-7180  

This document was last updated on March 1, 2014

Automatically included with all Retail Product Orders of $25 or More

### PAIN CREAM

### PAIN CREAM

Real Time Pain Cream is effective on deep muscle pain, cramps, and over 100 types of arthritis. Real Time Pain Cream works fast, smells great, and has no negative side effects, so it’s perfect to use any time of day.  Next time you’re in pain, instead of reaching for another pill with a warning label, try Real Time Pain Cream. 

### MAXX PAIN CREAM

### MAXX PAIN CREAM

Real Time Maxx is Real Time’s most powerful lotion! Real Time MAXX delivers fast Pain Relief to persistent, intense pain including deep muscle pain, cramps, and over 100 types of arthritis. Loaded with peppermint, Real Time MAXX provides a powerful burst of fast, minty pain relief.

### HAND PAIN CREAM

### HAND PAIN CREAM

Real Time Hand Cream is effective on many types of hand and wrist pains including carpal tunnel, deep muscle pains, cramps, and arthritis.  Real Time Hand Cream is made with nourishing Shea Butter and provides luxurious moisture with deep pain relief.  Apply often for soft skin and fast relief! 

### SPECIAL OFFERS

### SPECIAL OFFERS

Real Time Convenience and Special Offer Packages include a combination of our top pain relieving products, for home, and on the go. When you take advantage of these Specials, you’ll save at least 30%, plus receive FREE shipping! Made with Natures Ingredients, Real Time Products have no negative side effects. Take advantage of these great offers today!  

### FOOT PAIN CREAM

### FOOT PAIN CREAM

Real Time Foot Cream is effective on many types of foot and ankle pain including gout, planter fasciitis, bursitis, arthritis, and dry cracked feet. Made with Tea Tree Oil and Eucalyptus, Real Time Foot Cream delivers nourishing moisture with fast pain relief for the days that keep you on your toes.

### VEGAN PAIN RELIEF

### VEGAN PAIN RELIEF

Real Time SELECT gives you relief on the go for deep muscle pain, cramps, and over 100 types of arthritis. Infused with Raspberry Oil, Real Time SELECT is 100% vegan and comes in a convenient roll-on applicator. Real Time SELECT gives you pain relief on the go. 

### SPORTS CREAM

### SPORTS CREAM

Real Time Sports Cream provides fast relief for many kinds of pain including strained muscles, Runner’s knee, Bruises, Sprains, and Cramps. Real Time Sports Cream absorbs quickly and keeps you going by relieving pain fast.

### PET FORMULA

### PET FORMULA

Real Time Pet Formula is a revitalizing spray that helps your pet feel their best. Made with Aloe Vera and Menthol, Pet Formula provides a gentle cooling sensation. For happy pets, use Real Time Pet Formula.

* * *

What they say about Real Time Pain Relief

I give this stuff a 5 star rating because I had just had my tooth pulled and I was in severe pain nothing was helping not even my pain killers or icing it. 

I do not have any image to add but this RTPR really works and it is very concentrated. 

Have been using RTPR for only 3 weeks but my foot is feeling great.Have had trouble with the right foot for over 15 months;went to the foot doctor twice;he was no help. 

RTPR is a awesome product that just flat-out works without the concerns of getting addicted or worrying about harmful side-effects of oral pain medication or pain killers. Just rub it on the area where the pain is and that is all. 

I have osteoarthritis and the first thing in the morning, I put Real Time Pain Relief on my neck, shoulders, elbows, mid back, right hip, both knees and especially the right knee, both ankles and my right foot and toes. 

Lord this stuff gave me relief like no other I brought this stuff and will use nothing else. I quit my pain medicine cause this helped more than my Norco helped and faster. 

Submit Testimonial View All Testimonials

## STAY IN TOUCH

#### We are always available for you. You can call us or submit a support ticket and we will get back to you!  
Or, you can check us out on our social media pages. We want to hear from you!
